http://www.fetware.com/privacy.php?osCsid=3cb229801405a3d274a5f5b62c628dd1

Cart ContentsCheckoutMy Account
Welcome! Please log yourself in.Or create an account.
Catalog » Privacy Notice
Privacy NoticeYour privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.
Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.
Continue
Categories ALL Final Sale ItemsAdult Cloth DiapersNo-Wick Enclosed Elastic
PantsLined Waterproof Adult Plastic PantsLong Lasting Polyurethane PantsFull Cut Plastic Pants for Cloth DiapersPlastic Pants Made for DisposablesSnap-On Plastic PantsHi-Back Extra Coverage Plastic PantsLow Cut Plastic PantsGenuine Latex Rubber PantsTeen Youth Size Plastic PantsSenior Cut Plastic PantsMattress and Pillow CoversHard To Find ItemsPVC ClothingAB/DL Favorites
Featured Products Pearl Plastic Pants$9.95
Information
About Us FAQ Product Care Additional Size Info Shipping & Returns Privacy Notice Conditions of Use Contact Us
Shopping Cart 0 items
Reviews I have ordered these over the years and find them very comfo ..
Copyright © 2020 Fetware Products, LLC.Call us: +001 603-715-1035Phone Orders: Monday-Thursday 9:00am-5:30pm EST
Friday: 9:00am-3:00pm
